[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
No one's reading our blog, Mae.
没人看我们的博客，Mae。
Not no one. We got four hits.
不是没人。我们有四次点击。
Yeah, but two of them were me.
是啊，但其中两次是我。
There are still two more.
还有两次不是你。
Those were you.
那两次也是你。
Look, we started writing for FuzzFeed
听着，我们开始为FuzzFeed写博客
to keep students informed.
是为了让学生们了解信息。
[phone dings] - Ooh, we got a fifth.
[手机叮了一声] - 哦，我们有第五次了。
Still you, Mae.
还是你，Mae。
But no one's going to read it if they don't know about it,
但如果他们不知道，就不会有人去读，
so that is why I made this poster.
所以我才做了这张海报。
- If kids won't read our blog,
- 如果孩子们不读我们的博客，
what makes you think they'll read our poster?
你凭什么认为他们会读我们的海报？
Uh, the glitter.
呃，因为有闪粉。
[yelps]
[惊叫]
Good morning, ladies.
早上好，女士们。
Nicky, what are you doing in the school store?
尼基，你在这学校商店里做什么？
I'm the new manager. Welcome to...
我是新经理。欢迎来到...
Nicky's Get Schooly!
尼基的学园天地！
You made us tear our poster.
你把我们的海报撕了。
We're trying to get more readers for FuzzFeed.
我们正努力为FuzzFeed争取更多读者。
Yeah. Nobody read our last article.
是啊，没人看我们上一篇文章。
"Budget Cut Crisis: Head Janitor Now Also Lunch Lady."
《预算削减危机：校长现在也是午餐大妈》。
Spoiler alert, don't eat the mop bucket stew.
剧透警告，别吃拖把桶炖菜。
Hopefully more people will read our next article.
希望更多人会读我们的下一篇文章。
It's about school safety.
是关于学校安全的。
Yeah. Disaster preparedness.
对，灾难应对准备。
Next week is the anniversary of the Avalanche of 1975.
下周是1975年雪崩事件的纪念日。
Is that the one that made Pigfoot?
那是导致Pigfoot传说的那次吗？
You guys talking about Pigfoot?
你们在谈论Pigfoot吗？
Pigfoot's not real. It's just an urban legend.
Pigfoot不是真的，它只是一个都市传说。
What's an urban legend?
什么是都市传说？
It's a rumor that's been told so many times,
就是一个谣言被传了太多次，
people start to believe it's true.
人们开始相信它是真的。
Like if you swallow your gum,
比如如果你吞下口香糖，
it will stay in your stomach for seven years.
它会在你的胃里停留七年。
Or that you'll use math later in life.
或者你以后的生活中会用到数学。
I don't know anything about gum or math,
我对口香糖或数学一无所知，
but you guys should really write about Pigfoot.
但你们真的应该写写关于Pigfoot的事情。
Sorry, but we only write real news. The truth.
对不起，但我们只报道真实新闻。真相。
Important stuff. That's why our motto is...
重要的事情。这就是我们的座右铭……
Real news. The truth. Important stuff.
真实新闻。真相。重要的事情。
Exactly. Like Pigfoot.
没错。比如Pigfoot。
We're not writing about Pigfoot.
我们不写关于Pigfoot的报道。
- I am so proud of my students.
我为我的学生们感到非常骄傲。
You two with the reporting, you with the store,
你们两个负责报道，你负责商店，
and Ricky's keeping the halls safe.
而Ricky负责保持走廊的安全。
Keep up the good work.
继续保持优秀的工作。
Principal Tarian, those are 50¢.
Tarian校长，这些是50美分。
- Hmm.
嗯。
What does 37¢ get me?
37美分能买到什么？
About 13¢ away from a lollipop.
离一个棒棒糖还差13美分。
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇，哇，哇！
Yo, what are you doing?
喂，你在干什么？
I'm writing you up for running in the halls.
我要因为你在大厅里奔跑而记你一笔。
Come on, cut me some slack.
拜托，放我一马吧。
The law cuts no slack.
法律不留情面。
Take it up with the principal.
跟校长说去吧。
[sighs]
（叹气）
Ugh. Rough morning.
唉，今天早上真糟糕。
This hall monitor needs a lollipop.
这个走廊管理员需要一根棒棒糖。
Ooh, coffee and donut flavor.
哦，咖啡和甜甜圈口味。
So I just talked to the principal,
我刚和校长谈过，
and he told me I should be more like you.
他告诉我应该更像你。
Well, he's a smart man.
嗯，他是个聪明人。
So say hello to your new partner.
所以向你介绍你的新搭档。
What?
什么？
Ooh. Littering.
哦，乱扔垃圾。
Going to have to write you up for that.
得给你记上一笔了。
[upbeat music]
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling melody]
♪ ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Na, na-na ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪ ♪ 呐呐呐 ♪
[upbeat music]
[轻快的音乐]
Wow, that sash looks really good on you.
哇，那条绶带在你身上看起来真不错。
Which he's not supposed to be wearing when he's off duty.
按理说他下班时是不应该戴的。
Chicks really dig it.
妹子们真的很喜欢。
You know, there's a lot more to being hall monitor
你知道，当个风纪委员远不止是为了吸引‘妹子’。
than impressing "chicks."
好吧，那你就去做那些事，
Okay, well, you do whatever that stuff is,
我来负责搞定妹子们的事。
and I'll take care of the chick stuff.
看，完美的团队。好警察，好看警察。
See, the perfect team. Good cop, good-looking cop.
哦！我的绶带！
Oh! My sash!
See, if you were wearing it, that wouldn't have happened.
看，如果你戴着它，就不会发生这种事了。
Oh, Tom, here's a coupon for your bubble bath.
哦，汤姆，这是你泡泡浴的优惠券。
Oh, good, I'm out.
哦，太好了，我用完了。
Get the one in the teddy bear bottle.
拿那个泰迪熊瓶子里的。
It's the most manly.
那是最有男子气概的。
[baby talk] Who wants a treat?
[婴儿语]谁想要点心？
[babbles]
[咿呀学语]
Wow, I don't think Squishy likes these anymore. He used to gobble them right up.
哇，我觉得斯奎西不再喜欢这些了。他以前可是狼吞虎咽的。
Huh. Maybe they changed the recipe.
嗯。也许他们改了配方。
Uh, no. It's the same recipe.
呃，没有。配方还是一样的。
That's so weird.
真奇怪。
Here. Let's see.
来，我们看看。
What is going on, Anne?
安妮，这是怎么回事？
Why is he taking treats from you and not from me?
为什么他只从你那里拿零食，不从我这里拿？
Okay, Tom, this doesn't mean anything.
好吧，汤姆，这不代表什么。
He still loves you.
他仍然爱你。
Who said anything about him not loving me?
谁说他不爱我了？
Here you go, buddy.
给你，伙计。
[growls]
（低吼）
What did you say to him?
你对他说了什么？
Oh, man!
哦，天哪！
What's wrong, honey?
怎么了，亲爱的？
Did your wife turn your beloved pet against you too?
你妻子也让你心爱的宠物反对你了吗？
Uh, no.
呃，没有。
Mae and I posted a new article,
我和梅发了一篇新文章，
but it hasn't gotten any views yet.
但还没有人看过。
What's it about?
那篇文章是关于什么的？
School safety and the Great Avalanche of '75.
学校安全和1975年的大雪崩。
Ooh, so it's about Pigfoot.
哦，那是关于皮格福的。
It's not about Pigfoot!
不是关于Pigfoot的！
Half boy, half pig--
半人半猪——
it's scientifically impossible.
这在科学上是不可能的。
But stranger things have happened.
但更奇怪的事情都发生过。
I can't believe that story is still around.
我真不敢相信那个故事还在流传。
I know. It's so ridiculous. Where did it even come from?
我知道。太荒谬了。它到底是从哪儿来的？
[Tom] It happened just before your mom and I went to Edgewood.
[Tom] 那件事发生在你妈妈和我去Edgewood之前。
It was the '70s. The time of disco.
那是70年代。迪斯科的时代。
[disco music] - People wore their pants flared,
- 人们穿着喇叭裤，
their shoes high, and their hair big.
高跟鞋，还有大发型。
The only thing that mattered was the beat.
唯一重要的是节奏。
- Just get to Pigfoot.
只要去猪脚就行了。
[Tom] There was a student named Harry.
有一个学生叫哈利。
His family were pig farmers.
他的家人是养猪的。
All Harry wanted to do was tend his pigs and dance.
哈利只想照顾他的猪和跳舞。
He loved disco music,
他喜欢迪斯科音乐，
but the principal wouldn't allow it in the school.
但校长不允许在学校播放。
So he told Harry to take a hike.
所以他让哈利离开。
Well, Harry took the principal literally and set off
嗯，哈利真的听从了校长的话，带着
with his favorite pig Danny in search of a place
他最喜欢的猪丹尼出发了，寻找一个地方
where he could dance to his heart's content.
他可以尽情跳舞的地方。
But they got caught in the terrible avalanche.
但他们被可怕的雪崩困住了。
As they tumbled down the mountainside,
当他们沿着山坡滚下时，
they got squished together into one being:
他们被挤压在一起，变成了一个生物：
a boy with a pig nose,
一个长着猪鼻子的男孩，
a curly tail, and one pig foot.
卷曲的尾巴和一只猪脚。
Cursed to never dance again, Pigfoot lives a lonely life
被诅咒再也不能跳舞，猪脚过着孤独的生活
deep in the woods in a brick house
在森林深处的一座砖房里
where he's mighty mighty and letting it all hang out.
他非常强大，尽情展示自己。
So Pigfoot is real.
所以猪脚是真实存在的。
No, he's not real. It's a legend.
不，他不是真的。那只是一个传说。
And it's obvious hogwash.
而且显然是无稽之谈。
[all laugh]
（大家都笑）
- That was good. - Thank you.
——那很好。——谢谢。
Oh, Anne. Don't be such a ham.
哦，安妮。别这么矫情。
Get it, 'cause ham's like another word for pig?
明白了吗，因为‘火腿’就像是猪的另一种说法？
- Oh, we get it. - Not your best stuff.
——哦，我们明白了。——这不是你最好的表现。
[growls]
（咆哮声）
[upbeat music]
（欢快的音乐）
Our avalanche story got zero hits.
我们的雪崩故事点击量为零。
What are we doing wrong?
我们哪里做错了？
That poster had 4 pounds of glitter, Mae.
那张海报用了4磅的亮片，梅。
No, the left foot is the pig foot.
不，左脚是猪脚。
And he has a pig nose.
而且他有个猪鼻子。
And one of my dads says he breathes fire and farts lasers.
我其中一个爸爸说他能喷火和放激光屁。
I wish the school cared half as much about FuzzFeed
我希望学校对FuzzFeed的关注能有对那蠢猪男孩的一半。
as they do about that dumb pig boy.
我们得想得更大，梅。下一张海报，要镶满亮片。
We got to think big, Mae. Our next poster, bedazzled.
[倒吸一口气]
[gasps]
我们甚至可能用毛毡。
We may even use felt.
[倒吸一口气]
[gasps]
[倒抽一口气]
So you like it?
所以你喜欢它？
No, my asthma's acting up.
不，我的哮喘发作了。
That's better.
那样好多了。
That's a terrible idea!
那是个糟糕的主意！
Listen, kids like Pigfoot.
听着，孩子们喜欢猪脚。
You want more readers, write about Pigfoot.
你想吸引更多读者，就写关于猪脚的内容。
I don't know, Nicky. We're honest reporters.
我不确定，尼基。我们是诚实的记者。
Honesty doesn't pay the bills, honey.
诚实可不能付账单，亲爱的。
You got to give the people what they want.
你得给人们他们想要的。
I sell a lot more candy than carrot sticks,
我卖糖果比卖胡萝卜条多得多，
you know what I mean?
你知道我的意思吧？
We're better than that.
我们比那更好。
Yeah, but nobody knows we're better than that
是的，但没人知道我们比那更好
until they read our stuff.
直到他们读了我们的东西。
And to get them to read our stuff,
为了让人们读我们的东西，
maybe we need to write about Pigfoot.
也许我们需要写关于Pigfoot的内容。
[gasps]
[喘气]
Asthma?
哮喘？
No, shock. We're not writing about Pigfoot.
不，是震惊。我们不写关于Pigfoot的。
Look, if we can get some people to read FuzzFeed
看，如果我们能通过编造一些疯狂的故事来吸引一些人阅读FuzzFeed，
by making up a few crazy stories, is that so bad?
那有什么不好呢？
What about our motto?
那我们的座右铭呢？
Real news. The truth. Important stuff.
真实新闻。真相。重要的事情。
Once we hook them, we'll go back to that motto.
一旦我们吸引了他们，我们就会回到那个座右铭。
But until then, our new motto is:
但在那之前，我们的新座右铭是：
Less troof. More hoof.
少点真相。多点蹄子。
- How much hoof? [school bell rings]
- 多少蹄子？[学校铃声响起]
All right, come on, people, let's move it.
好吧，快点，大家，动起来。
I want these halls cleared. Get to class.
我希望这些走廊清空。去上课。
All right, let's go over SWERG again.
好吧，我们再来复习一下SWERG。
Stop.
停。
Write.
写。
Explain.
解释。
Rip.
撕。
Give. SWERG. You try it.
给。SWERG。你试试。
Who needs SWERG when you got swag?
有了swag，谁还需要SWERG？
Nobody's going to take you seriously with those sunglasses.
戴那些太阳镜，没人会认真对待你的。
Harper, no one is going to take you seriously...
哈珀，没人会认真对待你...
- Here it comes. - With that dirty sash.
- 来了。 - 带着那条脏腰带。
What is that? Soup?
这是什么？汤吗？
Pea.
豌豆。
You peed on your sash?
你尿在你的绶带上？
No. Pea soup.
不。是豌豆汤。
You ate in your sash?
你在绶带上吃东西？
You know you're not supposed to wear it off-duty.
你知道你不应该在非执勤时佩戴它。
[laughs] You said duty, sir.
你说了‘duty’，长官。
[chuckles] I did, didn't I?
我确实说了，不是吗？
Why can't you be more like your brother, huh?
为什么你不能更像你哥哥呢，嗯？
Clean sash, cool shades,
干净的绶带，酷酷的墨镜，
sophisticated sense of humor.
成熟的幽默感。
I salute you, Dicky.
向你致敬，迪基。
So what I took from that is, I'm your boss now.
我从那句话里理解的是，我现在是你的上司了。
You're not my boss!
你不是我的上司！
Watch this. I'm about to get my SWERG on.
看好了。我马上要进入我的SWERG状态了。
Stop! Do you have a hall pass?
停下！你有通行证吗？
I don't know. Do you have a wedgie?
我不知道。你有内裤夹吗？
'Cause that can be arranged.
因为那可以安排。
Okay. Just take this to the principal.
好吧。把这个交给校长。
Oh, Kedj, buddy, I get it.
哦，凯德，伙计，我明白了。
Nobody understands how annoying Sergeant Sweater-Vest can be
没有人比我能更理解针织背心警官有多烦人。
more than me.
尤其是我。
But he kind of has a point about the hall pass thing.
但他关于通行证的说法确实有点道理。
And we do have you on video giving wedgies.
而且我们有视频证据显示你给别人穿小鞋。
[muffled] You have video?
[含糊不清] 你们有视频？
Tons. But listen, if you go to the principal for this,
有很多。但听着，如果你因为这件事去找校长，
I'll make the wedgie thing go away. Deal?
我会让穿小鞋的事消失。成交？
Deal.
成交。
We don't have any video.
我们其实没有视频。
Well, it worked.
不过，这招奏效了。
Yes, but we can't lie like that.
是的，但我们不能那样撒谎。
Hall monitors need to hold themselves to a higher standard.
风纪委员需要对自己有更高的要求。
Look, Ricky, sometimes you have to break the rules
听着，里基，有时候你必须打破规则
to enforce the rules.
来执行规则。
Just try these on.
试试这些。
No, thanks.
不了，谢谢。
In my office, now.
现在来我办公室。
Nice job, Dicky. You're his boss now.
干得好，迪基。你现在是他老板了。
So you want to SWERG or you want to swag?
所以你是想装酷还是想耍帅？
Oh, I'll swag.
哦，我会耍帅。
But I am not happy about it.
但我对此并不感到高兴。
- [sighs] - Those are upside down.
那些是倒着的。
There's still some things I'm going to do my way.
还有一些事情我会按我的方式去做。
[upbeat music]
轻快的音乐
Okay, buddy, here we go. Ha ha!
好的，伙计，我们开始吧。哈哈！
- Squeaky toy? [toy squeaks]
吱吱响的玩具？
Non-squeaky toy?
不响的玩具？
- Okay, Tom, I fixed the transmission.
好的，汤姆，我修好了变速器。
What are you doing?
你在做什么？
I am trying to fix my relationship with Squishy. Money?
我正在努力修复我和Squishy的关系。钱？
Hey, that's my wallet.
嘿，那是我的钱包。
What is happening?
发生了什么事？
Squishy used to be man's best friend, and now he's Anne's best friend.
Squishy曾经是男人的好朋友，现在成了Anne的好朋友。
Oh, I don't think that's it. [laughs]
哦，我不觉得是那样。[笑]
No, maybe it is.
不，也许就是那样。
Our squishues started after we took him to the vet
我们和Squishy的关系开始恶化，是从我们带他去看兽医之后
and they put him in the cone of shame.
他们给他戴上了耻辱圈。
[growls]
[咆哮]
[barks]
[吠叫]
Hey, maybe you're right.
嘿，也许你是对的。
Maybe? I am right. And it's your fault. You're the one who made me take him to the vet.
也许？我是对的。这都是你的错。是你让我带他去看兽医的。
What? He had a hot spot.
什么？他有个热点。
Yeah, well, now he has a cold spot. In his heart. For me.
是啊，现在他心里有个冷点。对我。
Squishy, I am going to make it up to you. I am going to shame myself until you forgive me.
软软，我会补偿你的。我会让自己丢脸直到你原谅我。
[sighs] Tom, that is crazy.
叹气] 汤姆，那太疯狂了。
You're right. I'm going to need a bigger cone.
你说得对。我需要一个更大的锥子。
[upbeat music]
欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[phone dings]
手机叮了一声]
400 hits, Mae! Our plan worked!
400次点击，梅！我们的计划成功了！
Great. Now can we go back to writing the real news?
好极了。我们现在可以回去写真正的新闻了吗？
Absolutely. We've written our last fake story.
当然可以。我们写完了最后一个假新闻。
Say good-bye to Pigfoot.
跟Pigfoot说再见吧。
Get your Pigfoot products here. Only at Nicky's Get Piggy!
来这里购买Pigfoot产品。只在Nicky的Get Piggy有售！
We've got orange and green Pigfoot sticks.
我们有橙色和绿色的Pigfoot棒。
Those are just carrots and celery.
那些只是胡萝卜和芹菜。
Yeah, but I wrote "Pigfoot" on the label,
是的，但我把它们标为'Pigfoot'，
and now everyone wants to buy them.
现在每个人都想买它们。
So keep those Pigfoot articles coming.
所以继续推出那些Pigfoot的文章。
It's great for business.
这对生意有好处。
Awesome article.
很棒的文章。
I can't believe there was an actual Pigfoot sighting.
真不敢相信真的有人看到了猪脚。
Can't wait to read more about Pigfoot.
迫不及待想读更多关于猪脚的内容。
Actually, our next article is
实际上，我们的下一篇文章是
about the dangers of the playground.
关于操场的危险。
It's called "Splinters on the See-Saw:
题目是“跷跷板上的木刺：
"Why Recess Is a Pain in the Butt."
“为什么课间休息是个屁股痛的事。”
Eh, I'm not going to read that.
呃，我才不要读那个。
Tell us when you write about Pigfoot.
告诉我们你什么时候写关于猪脚的文章。
We'll have another Pigfoot post tomorrow.
我们明天还会有另一篇关于猪脚的帖子。
We will?
我们会吗？
We just got some new information.
我们刚得到了一些新信息。
We did?
我们得到了？
- Ooh, what is it? - Did you interview him?
哦，是什么？ - 你采访他了吗？
- Did you get him on video? - Did you touch his pig foot?
你拍到他视频了吗？ - 你摸了他的猪脚吗？
Yes, yes, and you'll just have to log on to find out.
是的，是的，你只需要登录就能知道了。
Oh, I will. I bet she touched the foot!
哦，我会的。我打赌她摸了那只脚！
A videotaped interview?
视频采访？
What happened to us saying good-bye to Pigfoot?
我们说再见给Pigfoot的事怎么办？
We did say good-bye.
我们确实说了再见。
But you know how sometimes your mom invites that one friend
但你知道有时候你妈妈会邀请那个特别的朋友
over for dinner, and you really don't want him to be there?
来家里吃饭，而你真的不希望他在那儿吗？
- But then 400 people-- [ding]
- 但随后400人-- [叮]
407 people want him to stay?
407人希望他留下？
Who are we to tell those people no?
我们有什么资格对那些人说‘不’呢？
We finally have readers, Mae. We can't lose them now.
我们终于有了读者，Mae。现在我们不能失去他们。
Well, you lost me. I quit.
好吧，你失去了我。我辞职了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Brenner, tuck in that shirt.
Brenner，把衬衫塞好。
Johanssen, no eating in the hall.
Johanssen，走廊里不准吃东西。
All right, Lanny, you ready to admit you're the litterbug?
好吧，Lanny，你准备好承认你是乱扔垃圾的人了吗？
[Lanny] I'm not the litterbug. I'm the gum chewer!
我不是乱扔垃圾的人。我是嚼口香糖的人！
Then who's the litterbug?
那么谁是乱扔垃圾的人？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇。
Are you putting students in lockers?
你在把学生关在储物柜里吗？
No.
没有。
Principal Tarian,
Tarian校长，
we both know sometimes you have to break the rules
我们都知道有时候为了执行规则，
to enforce the rules.
不得不打破规则。
No, you do not. You are a hall monitor.
不，你不是。你只是一个走廊监督员。
You need to hold yourself to a higher standard.
你需要对自己有更高的要求。
This is a clear abuse of your duty.
这是你职责的明显滥用。
[both] Ha ha, you said "duty."
[两人]哈哈，你说‘职责’。
It is not funny this time.
这次可不好笑。
You're both fired. Turn in your sashes.
你们两个都被解雇了。交出你们的肩带。
Aw, I guess we should have SWERGed.
唉，我想我们应该早点SWERGed。
Oh, well. You live, you learn.
哦，好吧。活到老，学到老。
Welcome to FuzzFeed.
欢迎来到FuzzFeed。
So, Mr. Foot...
那么，Foot先生...
[altered voice] Please, call me Pig.
[变声] 请叫我皮格。
May I touch your hoof?
我可以摸摸你的蹄子吗？
So what's the first thing you're going to do
你回到埃奇伍德后要做的第一件事是什么？
when you come back to Edgewood?
嗯，你知道，我想跳个舞
Well, you know, I want to boogie down
然后向校长复仇。
and get my revenge on the principal.
但如果有一件事我比迪斯科和复仇更爱，
But if there's one thing I love more than disco and revenge,
那就是尼基的“猪猪乐园”里的特价商品！
it's the bargains at Nicky's Get Piggy!
我们的视频火得不得了。FuzzFeed正在爆炸式增长。
Our video is crushing it. FuzzFeed is blowing up.
我怎么跟你说的？这头猪可大了，宝贝！大得很！
What did I tell you? The pig is big, baby! Big!
看！那不是我们最喜欢的记者吗！
Look! There's our favorite reporter!
[all cheering]
（众人欢呼）
Is Pigfoot really coming back to get revenge on the principal?
Pigfoot真的要回来向校长复仇吗？
Does he eat bacon?
他吃培根吗？
When he orders a BLT does he ask for a Me-L-T?
他点BLT三明治时会要求换成Me-L-T吗？
Don't worry. All your questions will be answered.
别担心，你们的问题都会得到解答。
Just keep checking FuzzFeed.
只需持续关注FuzzFeed。
Wait! But how did you find him?
等等！但你是怎么找到他的？
A real reporter never reveals her secrets.
一个真正的记者永远不会透露她的秘密。
You got a bright future, kid.
你前途无量，孩子。
A real reporter?
真正的记者？
So a real reporter dresses her brother up like a pig
所以一个真正的记者会让她的弟弟打扮成猪
and makes up a bunch of lies?
并且编造一堆谎言？
Well, you know what feels better than the truth?
那么，你知道什么比真相更让人感觉良好吗？
Nice job, Dawn.
干得好，Dawn。
That.
那就是。
I don't even know that guy.
我甚至不认识那个人。
And I don't even know you anymore.
我也不再认识你了。
It's all your fault.
这都是你的错。
We only got kicked off the force because we did things your way.
我们只是因为按照你的方式做事才被踢出警队的。
Well, at least we got to hang out together.
好吧，至少我们还能一起出去玩。
We're hanging from the lockers by our underwear.
我们现在是被内裤挂在储物柜上。
Together.
一起。
So what do you make of this Pigfoot business?
你怎么看这个猪脚事件？
Pigfoot's not real.
猪脚不是真的。
Of course Pigfoot's not real!
当然猪脚不是真的！
But just in case he is,
但万一他是真的，
I do not want that thing in my hallways.
我可不想让那东西出现在我的走廊里。
You're re-hired. Find him, get rid of him.
你被重新雇佣了。找到他，解决他。
Or your sashes are mine.
否则你的绶带就是我的了。
[both] Yes, sir!
是的，先生！
We're back.
我们回来了。
Oh, yeah. How are we going to get down?
哦，对。我们怎么下去？
I don't know.
我不知道。
[upbeat music]
（欢快音乐）
Come on, what's next for Pigfoot?
来吧，接下来Pigfoot怎么办？
You've always had good ideas. You can do this by yourself.
你总是有好主意。你可以自己搞定。
You don't need Mae.
你不需要Mae。
So you're really going to keep this going?
所以你真的要继续下去？
- Of course she's going to keep it going.
当然她会继续下去。
The pig is big, baby! Big!
猪脚大，宝贝！大得很！
And it's time to make it bigger.
现在是时候让它更大了。
No. It's time for Dawn to finally tell the truth.
不，现在是Dawn终于说出真相的时候了。
Don't listen to her. Give the people what they want.
别听她的。给人们他们想要的。
Don't listen to him.
别听他的。
He just wants you to keep lying,
他只是想让你继续撒谎，
so he can sell more stuff.
这样他就能卖更多东西。
- Pigfoot! - Truth!
- 猪脚！ - 真相！
- Pigfoot! [muffled shouting]
猪脚！
I know what I need to do.
我知道我需要做什么。
- Don't worry, Squish.
别担心，Squish。
As soon as Daddy's done putting this cereal away, we can--
爸爸一放好这盒麦片，我们就可以——
Well, I think Daddy's done with chores.
嗯，我想爸爸的家务活做完了。
So you want to go for a walk? What do you say?
所以你想去散步吗？你怎么说？
[growls]
（低吼声）
Why are you growling? I'm wearing the cone.
你为什么低吼？我戴着项圈。
I thought we were buddies again.
我以为我们又是好朋友了。
You know what, fine. I'm taking this thing off.
你知道吗，好吧。我要把这个东西摘下来。
Okay, Tom, I went to six different stores,
好的，汤姆，我去了六家不同的商店，
but I finally found your bubble bath.
但我终于找到了你的泡泡浴。
Wow.
哇。
- He-- - I don't care.
- 他-- - 我不在乎。
They were out of the no tears formula,
他们没有无泪配方，
so just be really careful
所以请非常小心
about getting your bubble beard in your eyes.
不要让你的泡泡胡须弄到眼睛里。
Oh. Thanks, Anne.
哦。谢谢，安妮。
I figured it was best to stay home
自从我因为戴着锥形帽开车被开了罚单后，
ever since I got that ticket for driving with a cone on.
我想最好还是待在家里。
[barking]
[吠叫]
Oh. Wait a minute.
哦，等一下。
I ran out of bubble bath at the same time we started having problems.
我正好在我们开始有问题的时候用完了泡泡浴液。
[barks]
[吠叫]
That's it!
就是这样！
It wasn't the cone at all, was it, boy?
根本不是因为那个锥子，对吧，孩子？
[barks]
[吠叫]
You missed our bubble baths, didn't you, buddy?
你怀念我们的泡泡浴了，对吧，伙计？
[barks]
[吠叫]
Woof! Woof!
汪！汪！
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
Nicky, I need your help.
尼基，我需要你的帮助。
- What's up? - Hang these up.
- 怎么了？ - 把这些挂起来。
I'm going to go give everybody what they want.
我要去给每个人他们想要的。
Pigfoot. In the flesh.
猪脚。亲自到场。
Happy to help.
很高兴帮忙。
This is a trick I know, sis.
这是个我知道的把戏，姐姐。
So, if Pigfoot shows up, you ready?
所以，如果猪脚出现，你准备好了吗？
He's not real, so yeah. I'm all set.
他不是真的，所以是的。我已经准备好了。
Psst!
嘘！
It's me, the principal.
是我，校长。
Look, I'm sure this Pigfoot stuff is all a hoax.
看，我确信这个Pigfoot的事情全是骗局。
But Dawn did print it in FuzzFeed,
但Dawn确实在FuzzFeed上发表了，
and we all know she always writes the truth.
我们都知道她总是写真话。
So I'm relying on you two and this mustache to protect me.
所以我依靠你们两个和这胡子来保护我。
Hey, Principal Tarian.
嘿，Tarian校长。
It's down to you two.
就看你们两个了。
Hello, hello.
大家好，大家好。
Thank you all for coming and for reading my articles.
感谢大家来这里，也感谢大家阅读我的文章。
We want Pigfoot.
我们要抓住Pigfoot。
[all yelling]
[所有人都在喊]
Okay, okay, okay, okay. Classmates.
好了，好了，好了，好了。同学们。
Who better to answer all your Pigfoot questions
还有谁能比
than Pigfoot himself?
Pigfoot本人更好地回答你们所有关于Pigfoot的问题呢？
[all] Pigfoot! Pigfoot! Pigfoot!
[所有人] Pigfoot！Pigfoot！Pigfoot！
Pigfoot! Pigfoot! Pigfoot!
Pigfoot！Pigfoot！Pigfoot！
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
Can you pig it?
你能做到吗？
[all] Yeah!
[所有人] 是的！
Nicky, what are you doing here?
Nicky，你在这里做什么？
You said you needed my help.
你说你需要我的帮助。
We're giving the school Pigfoot.
我们正在给学校举办猪脚活动。
I just wanted you to hang up the posters.
我只是想让你挂上这些海报。
Oh. Well, you live, you learn.
哦。好吧，活到老学到老。
[snorts and grunts]
[哼哼和咕哝]
We got him!
我们抓到他了！
He's real! He's totally real!
他是真的！他绝对是真的！
I can't believe he's real!
我简直不敢相信他是真的！
I knew he wasn't real.
我就知道他不是真的。
So he's a fake?
所以他是个假货？
So these are just regular carrots?
所以这些只是普通的胡萝卜？
Yeah. Dawn made the whole thing up.
是的。Dawn编造了整个故事。
[all] Boo!
嘘！
Sorry, Dawn.
对不起，Dawn。
No, Mae, you're right.
不，Mae，你说得对。
The Pigfoot that you all believed in,
你们都相信的那个猪脚，
the Pigfoot that I helped you believe in, is a lie.
我帮助你们相信的那个猪脚，是一个谎言。
FuzzFeed promised you real news.
FuzzFeed承诺给你们真实的新闻。
The truth. Important stuff.
真相。重要的事情。
But I broke that promise.
但我违背了那个承诺。
So, to make up for it, I spent all night doing research
所以，为了弥补这一点，我整晚都在做研究
and found the real Pigfoot.
并找到了真正的Pigfoot。
[all murmuring]
[所有人都在低声议论]
Hello, everybody. My name is Harry Kawalsky.
大家好，我叫Harry Kawalsky。
And as you can see, I have two normal feet.
如你们所见，我有两只正常的脚。
And I'm not a pig.
而且我不是一头猪。
[all] Boo!
[所有人]嘘！
- It may not be what you want to hear, but it's the truth.
这可能不是你们想听的，但这是真相。
Harry's family moved away from their pig farm
Harry的家人在雪崩那天离开了他们的养猪场，
the day of the avalanche,
所以大家都以为他被卷入了雪崩，
so everyone just assumed he got caught in it
所以大家都以为他被卷进去了
and fused together with his pig.
和他的猪融合在一起了。
It's an honest mistake.
这是个诚实的错误。
So there really is no Pigfoot.
所以实际上并没有什么猪脚。
[all] Aw.
哎呀。
But the dancing part is true.
但跳舞的部分是真的。
Now, who wants to learn to disco dance?
现在，谁想学跳迪斯科舞？
[all] Yeah!
耶！
[disco music]
迪斯科音乐
- Five, six, seven.
五、六、七。
♪ ♪
I'm sorry I got carried away. Be my partner again?
对不起，我有点忘形了。能再做我的舞伴吗？
Of course. Great work finding the true Pigfoot.
当然可以。你找到真正的Pigfoot做得很好。
Now that's real reporting.
这才是真正的报道。
[Ricky] No dancing in the halls!
[Ricky] 大厅里不准跳舞！
No dancing. No dancing.
不准跳舞。不准跳舞。
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪